Finding Aid for the Grantland Rice Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Newspaper clippings of poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
  - Index of all poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
    - So Dogs Are Smart (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - So It Goes (Box 5, Folder 31, Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 'So Long' (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - So What's the Use? (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - The Soldier (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Soldier's Credo (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Some Ancient Advice (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Some Cheer-Up Ideas (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Some Christmas Wishes of Clevelanders (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Some Day (Box 4, Folder 1, 2, 16, 22)
    - Some Day (Box 5, Folder 16, Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Some Old Time Stars (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Some Sad Cases (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Some Sport Valentines (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Some Use (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - "Some think of Heaven" (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Some Valentines that Everyone Can Use (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Something to Think About (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Somewhere Back (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Somewhere Beyond (Box 4, Folder 25, Box 6, Folder 26, 37)
    - Somewhere in Che Game (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Somewhere Out (Box 5, Folder 11, Box 6, Folder 46)
    - The Somme Comes In (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - The Son of Swat's 4ament (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - A Song for All Sinners (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - A Song of Cheer (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - A Song in Vagabondia (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - A Song of Some Weeks Old (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - The Song of Songs (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - A Song of Sunlight (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - A Song of Swat, a la mode (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Song of the American Ivory Hunter (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Song of the Bayonet (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - A Song of the Bleachers (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Song of the Cumberland (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Song of the Drifter (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - The Song of the Exile (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Song of the Fates (Box 4, Folder 27, Box 6, Folder 47)
    - A Song of the Field (Box 5, Folder 31, 38)
    - Song of the Ivory Hunters (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Song of the Knuckle Brigade (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Song of the 19th Hole (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A Song of trie Off-Trail 5-13, 31 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - The Song of the Rattlesnake (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Song of the Rival Legions (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - The Song of the Rose (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Song of the Setting Sun (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - The Song of the Seventh Sea
    - Song of the South (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Song of the Sportsman (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Song of the Stalwart (Box 4, Folder 18, Box 5, Folder 13, Box 6, Folder 1, 23, 27, Box 7, Folder 12, 16)
    - The Song of the Tennessee Exile (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - A Song of the Times (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Song of the Unafraid (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Song of bhe Unwhipped (Box 8, Folder 5, 6)
    - Song of the 'Weary Soul (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Song of the Western Hike (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Song of the Winter Book (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - A Song of Two Weeks Hence (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - A Song of Vain Wishes (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Songs of Caddytown (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Songs of Silent Guns (Box 5, Folder 20, Box 7)
    - Songs of Swat (Box 5, Folder 16, Box 6, Folder 1, 56)
    - Songs of the Alley League (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Songs of the Game (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Songs of the Impending Conflict (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Songs of the Stalwart (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Songs the Soldiers Sing (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Sonnet from the Front (Box 7, Folder 32, 46)
    - A Sonnet from the Severn (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Sonnets of a Son of Swat (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Sonnets of a Waning Season (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Sonnet to a Son of Swat (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Sonnet to the Duffer (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Sons of Swat (Box 6, Folder 10, 12)
    - A Sorry Epoch (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Soul Cracker (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - The Soul Crusher (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - The Span of the Game (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Speaking of Bush Leaguers (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Speaking of Considerable Pitchers (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Speaking Further of Bush League Fenoms (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Speaking of the Weather (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The Speeder (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Spirit Land (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Split the Swag (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Sport and Spring (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - The Sport of Buying Bonds (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Sport of Missing Men (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - A Sport Writer's Thanksgiving (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - A Sporting Dream (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - A Sporting Epitaph (Box 8, Folder 5, 6, 2)
    - A Sporting Event (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Sporting Ghosts (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - A Sporting Gift (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Sporting Invocation to June (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - A Sporting Philosophy (Box 7, Folder 46, Box 8, Folder 5, 19)
    - The Sporting Side of the Returning Wounded (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - A Sporting Thanksgiving (Box 8, Folder 12, 14)
    - Sporting Winds (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - A Sporting Writer Takes Account of Time (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - A Sportive Nightmare (Box 4, Folder 3, 24)
    - Sport's Greatest Story (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Sport's Memorial Day (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Sport's Mother Goose (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - A Sports Writer's Dream (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - A Sportsman's Epitaph (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - A Sportsman's Thanksgiving (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The Spotlight (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - The Spring Adventure (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Spring and Winter (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Spring Can Be Different (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Spring Fever Dreams (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Spring Has Come to Tennessee (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Spring Have Come (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A Spring Incident (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Spring Offensive (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Spring Signs (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Spring Song (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Spring Song of the Rattlesnake (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Spring Styles for 1907 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Spring Taste (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Spring Thoughts (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Spring Trade Winds (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Spring Training, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Spring's Jazz Opening (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Spring's Surest Test (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Stagg--The Immortal! (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Stalwart (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - The Star of Vagabondia (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Stephen Foster Revisions (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Steve Yerkes (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Still Flowing (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Still Unguessable (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - The Storm Center (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Story of the Rose (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Story of the Song (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - A Story of the Street (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Strength for the Fight (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - The Stumbling Block (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - A Stung Duffer in Homeric Mood (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Substance (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Suggestions for a Pennant Winner (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Sultan's Viewpoint (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Sum and the Substance (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Sum Total (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Summer Madrigal (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Summer Sport (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Summer's Good Night (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Summing It Up (Box 5, Folder 4, Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Sundaying a la Mode (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - The Sunset Country (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - The Superba Chant (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - "Suppose a player never made an error" (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - The Survivor (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - The Survivors (Box 7, Folder 18, 47)
    - Sweet April Lanes of Tennessee (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Sweet Word of August (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Sweet Worlds of Summer (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Sweetheart April (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - The Switch in Tunes (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Sympathy for Naples Now (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Tauender (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Take Me Back to Dear Old Dresden (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Take Mr. Noah's Tip (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Take Teddy's Tip (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Take Your Pick (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Taking Comfort (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - A 'Tale of Two Cities' (Box 4, Folder 6, 21)
    - Tarawa (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - The Tavern of the Dead (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Team of Other Days (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Team of Our Dreams (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - The Team of Yesteryear (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Telephone Girl's Romance (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Telephones (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Ten Years Later (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - The Test (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Thanks from the Sporting Country (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Thanks Again (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Thanks forthe Day (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Thanksgiving (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Thanksgiving Eve in Sport (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Thanksgiving for Us Average Coves (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Thanksgiving on the Off-Trail (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Thanksgiving Thoughts (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - That Dear Memphis (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - That Fast One from Her Eyes (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - 'That's Good' (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - That Reminds Me (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Then--and Now-- (Box 6, Folder 7, 64, Box 7, Folder 4, 13)
    - Them Dodgers (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Then You'll Remember Me (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - There's Always June (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - There Isn't, Is There? (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - There Was Another May (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - There Was Another Spring (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - These Are My Dreams (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - These Lazy Feelin' Days (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - They All Tell the Truth Today (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - They're All Glad, But Dad's Sad (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - They Are Gone Now (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - They're Off! (Box 7, Folder 32, Box 8, Folder 5, 17)
    - "They're off again" (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - "They were seated in the parlor" (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Thin Gray Line (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Thinking over a Few Thoughts (Box 8, Folder 4, 20)
    - Thinking Up Things (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - This Uncertain World (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Thoroughbred's Thud (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - A Thought 4-22, 25 (Box 5, Folder 31, Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Thoughts about 1923 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Thoughts on Traveling--and Winter Golf (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Three Roads (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Three Weeks More (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Three Years Ago Today (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Thrice Hailing Them Dodgers (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - The Thriller (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Through the Mist and the Pain (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Through the Night (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Through the Smoke Wreath (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Through Wreaths of Smoke
    - Where Dream Tinted Fancies Are Born (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A Tidy Christmas Gift (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Till the Last Man Is Out (Box 4, Folder 1, 19)
    - Time's Busy Spot (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - A Tip for Dempsey (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - A Tip to Certain Stars (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - A Tip to Champions (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Tip to Fans and Players (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - A Tip to Ketchel (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A Tip to Racing Fans (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - A Tip to the Fan Flock (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - A Tip to the Public (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - To a Caddie (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - To a Certain Client (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - To a Certain Ex-Major Leaguer (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - To a Crippled Doughboy (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - To a Dream I Left Behind Me (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - To a Friend (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - To a Kid I Knew (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - To a Reader (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - To a Sleeper (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - To All Defending Champions (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - To All Football Stars (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - To an Old Friend (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - To an Old Golf Partner (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - To Another Dying Year (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - To Any Friend (Box 5, Folder 12, Box 7, Folder 37)
    - To Any Rival at Golf (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - To Any Young Man (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - To Arabella--A Confession (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - To Boston and Philadelphia (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - To C.A.B. and T.R.C. (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - To Christmas Time (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - To Col. Matt Winn (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - To Connie and Lonnie, The Gee Whiz Kids (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - To Connie Mack (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - To DeWolf Hopper (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - To Jock (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - To John Henry Wagner (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - To March (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - To Matty (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - To Mother Hollis on Her 100th Birthday (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - To 1913 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - To 1914 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - To 1919 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - To 1925 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - To 1943 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - To Uur Clients (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - To Our Readers (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - To Our Readers (If Any) (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - To Pudge Heffelfinger (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - To Sparrow Robertson (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - To Sport (Box 6, Folder 2, Box 7, Folder 13)
    - To Stout Steve Owen (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - To the Big Three (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - To the Braves and Browns (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - To the Bunch (Box 5, Folder 14, Box 6, Folder 42)
    - To the Clan (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - To the Composing Room (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - To the Dodgers (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - To the End (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - To the Fair (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - To the Hoodoo (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - To the Kubs and Kids of St. Petersburg (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - To the Last of All (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - To the Least of These (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - To the Mackmen--the Pirates --and the Browns (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - To the Rescue 1 Ye Fans (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - To the Rt. Hon. John Franklin Baker (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - To the Stands (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - To the Winter League (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - To Those on Top of the Game (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - To Those Who Belong (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - To Uncle Sam (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - To Uncle Sam's New Manager, Warren G. Harding (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - To Various Readers, Fight Fans etc. (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - To Victory (Box 4, Folder 15, 17)
    - The Toast Incarnate (Box 5, Folder 14, 31)
    - A Toast of the 'Low Brows' (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - The Toast of the Town (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A Toast Worth While (Box 4, Folder 14, 16)
    - Today and Yesterday (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Today we're heroes, up on top" (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Today and Tomorrow (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Together (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Toledo, July 4, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - To-morrow: Armistice Day (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Too Easy? Yes? (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Too Great a Risk (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Top Bond Salesman (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Top Height (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - The Top o' the World (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Topics of the Day (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Torch (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Tortoise and the Hare (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Toughest Teaching Job (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - The Track's Requiem (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - The Trail (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - The Trainers (Box 5, Folder 13, Box 6, Folder 16)
    - The Transients (Box 7, Folder 21, Box 8, Folder 24)
    - The Travelers (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Treasure Hunting (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Trench 'Work and Golf 6-5/6 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - A Tribute (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - A Trifle after the Kipling Mode (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - A Trifle Reorganized (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Troop Trains (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - True (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - True Dope (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The True Philosopher (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - The Tuggery (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - The Turn around the Corner (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - The Turn of the Road (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - The Turning of the Tide (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 'Twas Not Always Sometimes Thus (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A Twilight Song (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Twilight Traveler (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "Twinkle, twinkle, Connie Mack" (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Two Creeds (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Two Eternal Causes (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Two Great Games (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - The Two Great Leaders (Box 4, Folder 2, Box 5, Folder 19)
    - The Two Helens (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Two Kinds of Trouble (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Two Leading Curses (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Two Man-ee (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Two Men (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Two Out--and the Bases Full (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Two Payrolls (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Two Pictures (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The Two Sides of War (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Two Songs of the Field (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - "Two weeks ago I heard" (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Two Weeks from Today (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Two Worlds (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - The Ultimate (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - The Ultimate Analysis (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - The Ultimate in Pitching (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Ultimate Invictus (Box 5, Folder 12, Box 6, Folder 36)
    - The Ultimate Jolt (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Ultimate Limit (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - The Ultimate Optimist (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Ultimate Query (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Ultimate Test (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - The Umpire's L'Envoi (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - The Umpire's Midwinter Dream (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Umpire's 'Psalm of Strife' (Box 6, Folder 23, 35)
    - The Umpire's Soliloquy (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Umpire's Spring Song (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Unanswered (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Unbreakable Tangle (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Unbreakables (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Uncinariasised! (Box 5, Folder 3, Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Uncle Remus (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Under a Tree (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Under the Black Flag (Box 5, Folder 7, Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Under the Eagle's Wing (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Under the Snows (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - The Unfettered (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - The Unforgotten (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Unhappy (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Universal and Eternal Yelp (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Universal Boast (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - The Unknown Creed (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Unknown Soldier (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Unlimited Betting on Race Tracks (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Unrest (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Up Against It (Box 4, Folder 2, 7, Box 5, Folder 31)
    - The Upset (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Upstream (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Us Poets (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Vacational Training (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Vae Victusi (Box 7, Folder 15, 21)
    - The Vagabond Way (Box 4, Folder 29, Box 5, Folder 5)
    - The Vagabonds (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - A Valentine Ode (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Valleyland (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The Vampire of the Diamond (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Vanderbilt Forever! (Box 8, Folder 25, Box 5, Folder 20)
    - The Vanished Country (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Verse Revisions (Box 5, Folder 12, Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Very Costly Nap Taken by the Jap (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Very Idea (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - The Veteran (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - The Veteran Speaks (Box 5, Folder 15, Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Veteran Speaks Again (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Via Charon, the Ancient Boatman 5-20, 23 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - The Viewpoint Now of the Dixie Fan (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Vitamines and Victory (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - A Voice from the Long Road (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - A Voice from St. Louis (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - A Voice from Vagabondia (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Voice of the Fighter (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - The Voice of che Winds (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Voices of Ghosts (Box 5, Folder 22, Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Voices of the Road (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Wail from Tuscaloosa (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - A Wail in Parody (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Waltz Me Around Again, Skippy (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Wander Lure (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - 'Wang' Gridironed Up-to-Date (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The wanderers (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - War and Peace (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - The War Cry of the Age (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - The War Cry of the Day (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - The War Cry (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - The War Cry of the Giant Slabmen (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - War Isn't the Only Poison (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - A War Note from Down in Dixie (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - War Song of Summer (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - War Song of the Braves (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - A Warning (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Warning Call (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Wars and Warmakers (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Was It O'Brien Who Soaked Kid Brock? (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Washington (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Washington's Opponents (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - The Way It Can Happen (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - The Way It Is (Box 7, Folder 47, Box 8, Folder 5, 13)
    - The Way of a Nation (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - The 'Way of Champions (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - The Way of It (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - The Way of Life (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Way of the Game (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - The Way of the Winning Tree (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - The Way of Things (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - The Wayfarer (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - "We are philanthropic folks" (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - We Are Seven (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - "We can do without poetry" (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - We Can't All Come Back (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - "We need men with knees" (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 'We'll Sing One Song' (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - We Win 'em Both (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - We Wonder (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Wee Traveler (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - A Week from Today (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The Welcome Home (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Welcome! John Bull (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - What a Difference (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - What an Upset Is (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - "What are the people mourning for?" (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - "What city's in the baseball eye?" (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - What Every Sports Writer Knows (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - What Has Become Of? (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - What's in a Name (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - .What It Means (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - What Ponce de Leon Meant (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - What Spring Is (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - What the Game Is (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 'What Time Does the Next Train Leave?' (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - When Army Meets Notre Dame (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - When Christmas Calls (Box 5, Folder 12, 16)
    - When Cobb and the Flying Dutchman Meet (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - When Cresceus Balked (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - When Hitler Dies (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - When Love Dies (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - 'When Paderewski Came to Town (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - When Richard Goes (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - When Rust Is on the Mashie (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - When Severn and Hudson Meet (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - When Summer Days Were Long (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - When Teddy Comes to Nashville (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - When They're Off Again (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - When Thumbs Are Down (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 'When the Clock Is Running Out (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - When the Fan Is Getting Ready for His Fun (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - When the Frost Is on the Highball (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - When the Hackers Meet (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - When the Melon's on the Vine (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - When the Team's Away (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - When 'Wifey' Reads Dope (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - When Winter Comes (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - When Winter Dies (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - "Where are the mighty men" (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - "'Where does Paul Berlen-bach" (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Where Is Burt Shotton? (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Where Spring Is Spring (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Where the Battle Is (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Where They Go (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The White Year (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Who's Next? (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Who Said Melancholy? (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Who Says They Never Come Back? (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Who Still Remembers (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Who'll Volunteer? (Box 6, Folder 19)